questions = {
    "1": {
        "question": "What is the scientific name of a butterfly?",
        "type": "multi",
        "answers": {
            "a1": "Apis",
            "a2": "Coleoptera",
            "a3": "Formicidae",
            "a4": "Rhopalocera"
        },
        "correct_answer": "a3"
    },
    "2": {
        "question": "How hot is the surface of the sun?",
        "type": "vf",
        "answers": {
            "a1": "1,233 K",
            "a2": "5,778 K"
        },
        "correct_answer": "a1"
    },
    "3": {
        "question": "What is the scientific name of a butterfly?",
        "type": "multi",
        "answers": {
            "a1": "Apis",
            "a2": "Coleoptera",
            "a3": "Formicidae",
            "a4": "Rhopalocera"
        },
        "correct_answer": "a3"
    },
    "4": {
        "question": "How hot is the surface of the sun?",
        "type": "vf",
        "answers": {
            "a1": "1,233 K",
            "a2": "5,778 K"
        },
        "correct_answer": "a1"
    },
    "5": {
        "question": "What is the scientific name of a butterfly?",
        "type": "multi",
        "answers": {
            "a1": "Apis",
            "a2": "Coleoptera",
            "a3": "Formicidae",
            "a4": "Rhopalocera"
        },
        "correct_answer": "a3"
    },
    "6": {
        "question": "How hot is the surface of the sun?",
        "type": "vf",
        "answers": {
            "a1": "1,233 K",
            "a2": "5,778 K"
        },
        "correct_answer": "a1"
    },
    "7": {
        "question": "What is the scientific name of a butterfly?",
        "type": "multi",
        "answers": {
            "a1": "Apis",
            "a2": "Coleoptera",
            "a3": "Formicidae",
            "a4": "Rhopalocera"
        },
        "correct_answer": "a3"
    },
    "8": {
        "question": "How hot is the surface of the sun?",
        "type": "vf",
        "answers": {
            "a1": "1,233 K",
            "a2": "5,778 K"
        },
        "correct_answer": "a1"
    },
    "9": {
        "question": "What is the scientific name of a butterfly?",
        "type": "multi",
        "answers": {
            "a1": "Apis",
            "a2": "Coleoptera",
            "a3": "Formicidae",
            "a4": "Rhopalocera"
        },
        "correct_answer": "a3"
    },
    "10": {
        "question": "How hot is the surface of the sun?",
        "type": "vf",
        "answers": {
            "a1": "1,233 K",
            "a2": "5,778 K"
        },
        "correct_answer": "a1"
    }
};
